And so what I did was, I gave talks
on the Meadows, like for
free and I just sometimes,
some of my friends turned up, sometimes I
had an audience and I just gave this
talk and because it was on the Meadows
and I didn't have any problems with the
venue, I gave it two or three times
an afternoon for about a week or so.
Then one of my friends who I'd been
doing some opening stand-up for, he
got COVID and so he
rang me up and he said,
I'm not doing my show tonight, so
do you want the spot?
And I said, yeah sure.
So what I did was, I went out in
front of a bunch of
people who were expecting
a topical comedy evening and said, oh
actually I'm not the guy you're expecting
tonight and I'm going to tell you
about project management
for an hour and if
you want to leave you can.
And nobody left which is
amazing and so kind of like,
I'd been kind of talking
through this thing for about a week and
then I got to do one performance and
then I got COVID. So I was like
kind of bedridden for the next week.